Kwang Soo.
Yes, sir!
Why do all the people that I love leave me like this?
For you
I must have been a bad guy.
Ji Hee! Don't forgive me.
What should I do? I don't want to lose her.
What should I do?
That's okay. That's okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't say sorry again.
I'll not let you go.
I can lose everthing but you.
Don't think about anything else. Just stay with me.
I have to go now.
I need to meet someone.
You just stay here.
Don't go anywhere.
I'm not ordering you. I'm asking you.
That's good.
I'm shameless, aren't I?
You can't control
who you fall in love with.
Let's go inside.
Min Hyuk!
Your father is tired.
If you do this.
Just forgive me this once.
I won't marry Se Yeon.
How can you do this under such a circumstance?
I know you've treated me well,
but for all these years,
I never had anything I really wanted.
If you're not going to marry Se Yeon
and take over this company, then get out.
I want to protect that girl.
I don't want to hear about it. Get out!
I'll take care of what I am in charge of now.
Are you really going to let him go?
Don't worry. He'll come back.
He's my son.
I know him better than anyone.
He's different this time.
Go investigate the girl throughly.
Yes, sir!
How did it go?
Like Ms. Kang said,
she almost hit a truck on the night of the accident.
Why didn't the driver say anything to the police?
What about the drum?
His truck was overloaded,
so he didn't want to get in trouble.
Any evidence?
He doesn't have a black box,
and because it was raining that day, he couldn't recognize the driver.
Did he tell anyone
about that accident?
I don't think so.
When I asked him about it, he remembered.
See him again.
If there isn't an evidence then make one.
You remember that?
But...
I know the truth.
Ahn Do Hoon was driving that day.
I don't know if I should do this.
Thank you.
I hope this will help you. I have to go.
On the day my father disappeared. Where did you go?
- Get off! - What were you thinking about while driving?
Thinking about where you can dump my father?
Get off!
What might this be?
- What are you doing? - What am I doing?
You don't know it as a lawyer?
What? When you dumped my father,
you didn't think this would happen?
You said I was dragging you down.
No! What you did yourself is dragging you down.
I went to see President Jo.
These are files about you.
Two pages. They didn't care about your hard working days.
Your education, asset, family relations,
and your record as an ex-convict.
That's what they want to know about you.
Do you want to date with Jo Min Hyuk?
- That's none of your business. - Are you trying to make drag him down just like you did to me?
If Min Hyuk chooses you, he'll lose everything.
- If that happens, I'll be glad. - Shut up!
Pull yourself together, you know what your problem is?
Because of that damn love, you can't even see your own future clearly.
I'm glad you're here. I wanted to see you.
Who do you think people will side with between you and me?
Don't think who he likes
is more important than other people's thought?
You seem very confident.
This marriage won't make either of you happy.
Don't you think you are the one who cause it?
Stop using Min Hyuk.
You can't use other man to keep the man who left you.
Do you regret breaking up with Do Hoon?
Is that why you don't want to leave?
I don't regret breaking up with him.
I wish I had let him go earlier.
I knew he didn't love me, but I was foolish to keep him.
Trying to keep someone who doesn't love you is imposition, not love.
How dare you!
Since you slapped me, I'll say one more thing.
You're going to marry soon,
but you don't look happy.
Have you been waiting long?
It's what I do well.
You didn't know when I'd come.
You should've called me.
You're lonely without me following you around?
Did something happen?
I couldn't reach you all day.
Nothing happened.
What about you?
Something happened, but I forgot about it as soon as I saw you.
You're not dressed warmly enough. I want to walk a little bit longer.
- You'll get cold. - I'm not cold.
I worked at a ski resort in winter,
and I'm used to cold weather. This is a piece of cake.
Is there anything you haven't done?
It's too sweet for me.
It'll warm you up.
I'm not going to marry her.
Why don't you say anything?
It's because of you. So you can't run away from me.
Thank you and I'm sorry.
You shouldn't thank me. I should thank you.
Well...
Other couples will do that...
Lean on my shoulder.
You live alone on an island all by yourself.
All of a sudden, three girls appear.
No. 1, she's pretty but she's idealistic.
No. 2, she's soft inside, but tough outside.
All of a sudden.
Oops!
Who is she? She is very sexy with a bright smile.
She's the third girl.
Look at me! Look at me!
One, two, three! Go!
You're a wise man. Who would you choose among these three?
Sandra! What are you doing?
There aren't three girls here. I'm the only girl here.
You two are too old for him.
Hey! We're not that old.
Older women are still women.
Can you be young forever?
You guys are drinking again.
What are you doing here?
It's way past his working hours. Don't be so strict
He doesn't work for you 24 hours a day.
Sir,
you've become more handsome.
By the way, it's really late at night,
so can I ask what you did with Yoo Jung and where you took her?
Are you a detective? It's none of your business.
Why do you come back so early?
You only have these snacks?
I'll go make some more.
Why you?
Sit here.
Madam, why don't you go make some?
Hey!
I look older because of my hair style,
If I straghiten my hair up, I'll look as young as her.
Kwang Soo, what is she talking about?
I think she'd be prettier with straight hair.
Sit!
Oh my god. You have a weird taste.
Unbelievable!
I understand. Don't say anything.
Calm down. Come on.
Check the liabilities for me.
I'll call you back.
Se Yeon.
President Jo seems worse than I thought.
The operation went well.
We're waiting for the result.
I told you that no one knew Min Hyuk better than me.
No matter how crazy he is about her,
he can't abandon his family.
Shake up the K Corporation.
If his father falls, he'll come back.
It might take longer than you think.
I'm not that stupid, sir.
I've made a plan.
I'll talk to Min Hyuk.
I've heard what you said.
What did my father say?
He's not well enough.
He needs to rest for a while.
We're telling the press that he's busy checking into the resort business.
While I'm in jail,
if you don't take of of the company,
then it'll be hard to develop.
We knew this would happen.
But we're messed up because we aren't fully prepared.
You need to be in charge.
Gwang Min, I already told you.
I'm not going to change my mind...
This is the key to the safe deposit box.
You keep it while I'm in jail.
Gwang Min!
Whether you like it or not,
you're the heir to the K Corporation.
The file you wanted about Ahn Do Hoon
is in the safe deposit box.
Although he helped us a lot,
but he knows too much about us.
We don't know when he might betray us.
When he becomes a threat to us,
the files might help you.
Sir!
You think I didn't see you.
Smile.
Smile for me.
I'll go after I see your smile.
I have to go.
Se Yeon! Se Yeon!
You come to me only when you need me.
Why did you do that?
So what?
This isn't enough to destroy the K Corportaion,
but Se Gwang and Shina aren't going to let this good opportunity slide.
What are you planning now?
You must be aware of
what I am planning.
I won't give up what I have,
If you want to keep your company,
side with me.
What are you talking about?
If I lose my company,
your father will be the first one to against our marriage.
Isn't that what you want?
What I want is you.
You! It's you!
Don't tell me that you didn't know.
When you were down because of your mother,
when your father kicked you out,
when Seo Ji Hee died,
It was me who sided with you.
Se Yeon.
I love you.
I love you. I love you. I said I love you.
I'm sorry.
You and that girl,
do you think you'll have a good ending?
You asked me how love that started from revenge would end.
I'll show you how it ends.
Here are some more peppers.
Thank you.
Okay.
Welcome.
Can I have a bowl of soup?
We're closing soon. Just leave.
People are still eating.
Just give me one.
She's a customer. What're you doing?
Go take her some.
Where do you think you are?
You're early.
Do you want some too?
Let's talk after we eat.
You even asked Do Hoon to come here.
What do you want?
Are you trying to ruin our business?
Mother. Don't worry.
Get out.
Let's go outside and talk.
Why?
Why can't we talk here?
Okay. Let's talk here.
Now, he's found a girl, and his life is getting better.
Why on earth are you here?
A girl?
Yes, she is a kind girl.
She's a painter,
and she's nothing like you.
Please stop.
Shin Se Yeon.
You think they are well matched.
Do you think her parents will approve of that?
Go outsie with me.
Now.
Do Hoon!
Stop!
What?
How dare she think that Do Hoon isn't good enough?
Let them talk themeselves.
They were deeply in love.
In love?
Stop thinking about that.
They had a kid.
You can't just make that go away.
Don't give her a reason to cling to him.
It's useless for you to do this.
The evidence that you have won't prove anything.
Is that so?
Should I go to the press, then?
You like to be on TV.
No matter what you do, it won't work.
How can I stop you?
Should I destroy Jo Min Hyuk completely?
You can never destroy him that easily.
At least, I can see his true heart.
True heart?
You're still living in a dream.
Do you still believe in stuff like that?
I do.
I take pity on you who doesn't believe it.
How poor you are.
This won't end here.
I'll bring you to court, no matter what it takes.
In the place you worshiped so much,
you'll have to confess to your crime.
Have you heard that?
President Jo's legal advisor has been arrested.
Our company might go bankrupt.
I saw the newspaper article.
It's serious.
What should I do?
Did you see it?
What's going to happen to us?
I don't know.
- Yoo Jung. - Yes.
They said our restaurant is going to be sold,
is that true?
Kang Yoo Jung.
You seem quite close to Mr. Jo.
Have you heard anything from him?
We received the investment,
and the customers speak highly of our menu.
We'll be okay.
You don't know anything.
Our restaurant is doing fine.
It's headquarters that's in trouble.
They'll sell the restaurant chain first.
We'll have a new owner?
What if they fire all of us?
I'm finished this time.
If I don't pay my rent again,
Ja Yeong will kill me.
- I bought a new purse last month. - I'm not feeling well.
Somone sent this file to the board.
I knew it would be you.
It was too obvious and was no fun.
I just told them the truth.
I didn't do anything good.
I'm not going to talk about this.
Get Attorney Choi Gwang Min
out of jail!
I will try.
You'll have to.
He has some files about you.
Who knows?
If you prove that you're useful to our company,
even if you were arrested for a hit-and-run,
Gwang Min might get you released.
And this.
Listen to it when you have time.
It's the testimony of the truck driver.
You'll enjoy it.
It'll refresh your memory
of what you have down before.
It's more difficult that I thought.
The painting you gave to the Director of the NTS,
was purchased by the Shina Foundation.
If they investigate it thoroughly,
it might be diffcult to stop it.
So?
This is your chance.
I'll get you out.
Are you going to give up your life
for President Jo and his son?
I don't think you're genuinely concerned about me.
What is it that you want?
I heard you have files about me.
I loved martial arts novels.
But the story is always the same.
The right-hand man always betrays the boss.
Give the files to me.
You are similiar to me.
We were born with nothing,
but are quiet smart. That's why we're here.
Do you know the difference between us?
This is your last chance.
I don't betray people over something that doesn't belong to me.
Isn't it too obvious?
We've seen it in books and in real life too many times.
Gwang Min!
I really want to be this kind of guy,
who protects what he should protect,
instead of saving himself.
In real life, not in books.
Jae Ha!
How clumsy of you
to take pictures like this?
It's your brother,
- who took them. - What?
Your brother wnats to buy the shares of Se Gwang Heavy Industry.
While you're trying to destroy our company,
your brother has been making the shares that you have useless.
Why are you telling me this?
I know we don't like each other.
When I see you, I want to quarrel with you.
You and I are both awful people,
but we should stop acting like dogs.
Did you spread rumors about my father?
What's your point?
Okay.
I'll put these down.
I think your brother and
the Shina Hotel are up to something.
I like you better than your brother.
What do you want from me?
Call me when you want to have a drink.
Do you think I will not buy the restaurant as along as you did it?
This is why you don't have a friend, you idiot!
Have a seat.
I have something to tell you.
We can skip the usual greetings.
Min Hyuk is not going to marry Se Yeon because of you.
Did you hear what happened to our company?
Gwang Min is like an old brother to Min Hyuk.
He's sacrificing himself for the company to protect Min Hyuk.
What do you think Min Hyuk will feel at the moment?
I'm sorry.
If you're sorry, leave.
Do you want to destroy the company his father has built?
I made a promise.
I'll not leave,
until he tells me to leave.
Don't you understand what I'm talking about?
I'm sorry.
I have a way of making you understand.
I'll see you later.
Do it tomorrow,
why do you have to do it now?
I'll become lazy if I leave it tomorrow.
I'm done.
Aren't you tired?
No.
Are you guys going to be okay?
Ja Yeong. I don't deserve to be happy, do I?
I thought one day was enough,
but I want him more.
You've been sufferd a lot, you can be happy now.
It's okay, if I hadn't gone to jail,
I wouldn't have met you guys.
And Min Hyuk.
It's enough as long as you're happy now.
Let's go to sleep.
This will hurt the Shina Foundation as well.
Do you know that?
I know.
This will hurt not only the K Corporation, but you as well.
I can't do that.
Do as I say.
Why are you doing this?
I want to see Min Hyuk kneel in front of me and beg for my mercy.
But, you'll get hurt first.
Do what I want you to do.
I can't.
I'll make Min Hyuk kneel in front of you and beg for your mercy.
I like your loyalty.
So...
When I am completely alone,
will you hold me in arms?
I will.
You're pretty.
You're prettier when you smile.
I'm afraid I'll fall asleep before you come, so I drank a lot of sweet coffee.
I feel good now.
Yoo Jung.
Yes.
Don't die before me.
I won't.
Father, what are you doing here so late?
What is this, Do Hoon?
Tell me this isn't true, and it wasn't you.
Father. Don't worry about it.
How can I not? What is it?
It says that you dumped Yoo Jung's father. What is this all about?
Yoo Jung is doing this because she can't accept the fact that we broke up.
It's not a big deal.
How can you say that?
You saw her at the restaurant.
She's changed. She's crazy.
Do Hoon... Are you really my son?
I have a meeting. You should go.
I need to see Yoo Jung.
I'll figure it out.
If she's mad at us,
we need to apologize and beg for gorgiveness.
What are you talking about?
You've lived all your life as if you had done something wrong.
I don't want to live like you. Don't go to see Yoo Jung.
I'll take care of it.
You should go now.
Isn't it enough to get Min Hyuk involved? You even went to see my father?
What should I do to stop you?
I don't want to stop yet. You're still up there, safe and sound.
What happened to your father was an accident.
Choose the right word. It wasn't an accident, it was a murder.
There isn't enough evidence.
If I can't bring you to court, I'll go to the press.
If the press can't spread it,
I'll follow you everywhere until I destroy you.
I'm sorry.
That's easy.
I'm sorry, Yoo Jung!
I'll see you in court tomorrow. You know the place well.
You know how to get there.
I told you. It was an accident. It wasn't my fault.
You always said it wasn't your fault.
Your parents, me and rich people are to be blame.
Nobody else but you put you in this position.
Don't blame others.
What are you doing here?
I smell something stinky.
Leaving so soon? Why don't you stay?
Your friend is coming.
Hye Jin. Lee Hye Jin.
You wrote her a letter of recommendation. I thought you two were close.
Se Yeon!
Do Hoon!
I can't...
I can't let it end here.
Are you here to see my father? He's busy with the resort development.
Is he sick again?
Why are you here?
I hope he gets better before our wedding.
Why are you doing this to me?
You don't know? I want to help your company,
which is in crisis.
I don't need your help. I'll talk to your father.
No.
Yes, you're right. Thank you for having been there for me,
but I can't marry you.
I don't want to feel guilty about you and Yoo Jung for the rest of my life.
What should we do? I want you to be with me.
I want you live a miserable life.
Se Yeon.
Don't try to call me that gentle. It's not you.
Do you talk to her in a sweet voice like that?
What? Are you scared?
Why does Mr. Ahn come here?
The painting bribe of Shina Gallery that Mr. Choi was engaged in.
If I reveal those who were involved, it'll cause a big stir.
But don't worry. I can stop it.
What are you doing?
This company that your father has built
might collapse.
Your loyal dog, Choi Gwang Min.
He might have to be jailed for 10 years instead of a few months.
This puts you in danger as well.
K Corporation lost 2.5 billion KRW investing money in the painting.
The procuratorate will think that you embezzled that money to create slush funds.
Give the phone to Min Hyuk.
Listen to me.
I'm the most qualified person to defend you.
I'm the one who can protect Mr. Jo.
The lawyer from the Legal Team of the K Corporation.
Ahn Do Hoon.
What are you going to do?
What are you doing here?
Both you and I are in danger.
Choose between living together, or dying together.
Shin Se Yeon!